<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Programming Projects on Seoyeong Park</title>
    <link>https://seoyeongpark.github.io/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Programming Projects on Seoyeong Park</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>utf-8</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 16:47:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://seoyeongpark.github.io/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Course scheduling with CSP</title>
      <link>https://seoyeongpark.github.io/projects/courseschedulingcsp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seoyeongpark.github.io/projects/courseschedulingcsp/</guid>
      <description>Project design The objective of this project is to help students design and simulate their course schedules based on given the dataset of the course listing.
The course scheduler is considered as a constraint satisfaction problem by checking schedule conflicts and requirements to generate a feasible schedule with minimizing unsatisfied preference. We have assumed that every student must enroll as a full-time student, and they have a maximum credit limit. Each course contains information about time, prerequisites, instructor, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discord bot - StockImpulse</title>
      <link>https://seoyeongpark.github.io/projects/stockimpulse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seoyeongpark.github.io/projects/stockimpulse/</guid>
      <description>Project design StockImpulse is a fast and easy to use discord bot for getting stock information. This means that users will have access to information about US stocks from their discord account. StockImpulse also allows users to look up information about crypto currencies. StockImpulse allows for up to 60 stock requests every minute and 50 requests every 10 minutes for cryptocurrency.
Instruction Refer to the official instruction
APIs  The Finnhub API is used for information regarding stocks alongside the finnhub-python python package.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slash - Price comparison web</title>
      <link>https://seoyeongpark.github.io/projects/slash/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seoyeongpark.github.io/projects/slash/</guid>
      <description>Project design Slash is a website that scrapes the most popular e-commerce websites to get the best deals on the searched items across these websites.
 Fast: With slash, you can save over 50% of your time by comparing deals across websites within seconds Easy: Slash uses very easy commands to filter, sort and search your items Powerful: Quickly alter the commands to get desired results Informative: Provides the information about items through an email with attached csv file  Instruction Refer to the official instruction</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>