<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Statistical Modeling on Seoyeong Park</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/statistical-modeling/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Statistical Modeling on Seoyeong Park</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>utf-8</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 19:33:43 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/statistical-modeling/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Correlation Between Emotional Transition and Vocabulary Usage in Individual Social Media Posts Using NLP</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/research/emotion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 19:33:43 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/research/emotion/</guid>
      <description>&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;summary-and-goal&#34;&gt;Summary and goal&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Emotion modeling of event-based mental states changing using topic modeling&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Understanding word attribution and vocabulary usages for emotional shifts&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Discovering discernible changes in writing style depending on emotional shifts in online communication and social media posts&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Envisioning a conditional random field (CRF) that captures transitions in emotional states to create an empathetic language suggestion model that generates comforting and supportive responses to users&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;analysis-of-the-correlation-between-emotional-fluctuation-and-usage-of-words&#34;&gt;Analysis of the Correlation Between Emotional Fluctuation and Usage of Words&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In today&amp;rsquo;s digital age, online communities like Reddit play a significant role in providing emotional support and a sense of belonging to individuals dealing with various life situations and struggles. Users often express their feelings, emotions, and experiences on different subreddit communities and are provided with empathetic responses. Harnessing the valuable data generated within these communities is crucial in gaining insight into human emotion.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
