<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Seoyeong Park</title>
    <link>https://seoyeongpark.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Seoyeong Park</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>utf-8</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://seoyeongpark.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Challenges Faced by Older Adults in Using Mobile Apps and a Way Forward</title>
      <link>https://seoyeongpark.github.io/publications/elderly-accessibility/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://seoyeongpark.github.io/publications/elderly-accessibility/</guid>
      <description>&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;abstract&#34;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The low adoption of mobile apps by older adults exacerbates the digital divide. We examine the psychological and technological factors that influence app usage by older adults, drawing insights from app reviews to highlight the unmet needs of older adults and their expectations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;resources&#34;&gt;Resources&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/document/11370806&#34;&gt;Paper&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEAL: Model of Empathy Augmented Logistics for Food Security</title>
      <link>https://seoyeongpark.github.io/publications/food-sharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://seoyeongpark.github.io/publications/food-sharing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;abstract&#34;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Millions globally lack access to nutritious food, experiencing food insecurity. Despite growing recognition and efforts, equitable distribution remains hard due to limited resources and the diverse preferences of users. The problem of equitable food distribution requires a robust, socially intelligent infrastructure. We propose Meal (Model of Empathy Augmented Logistics for Food Security), a novel approach based on a multistakeholder recommendation system for food allocation, balancing user needs and society&amp;rsquo;s sustainability. Unlike existing systems that focus on either user satisfaction or logistical operations, our model considers both users and food banks, dynamically adapting to changing preferences and resource availability. Our simulated experiments demonstrate improvement in metrics such as over single-stakeholder models, suggesting significant potential for improved food access and resource utilization in addressing food insecurity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clustering-Based Multitask Classification for Predictive Consumer Behavior Modeling</title>
      <link>https://seoyeongpark.github.io/publications/ml-nagoya/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://seoyeongpark.github.io/publications/ml-nagoya/</guid>
      <description>&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;abstract&#34;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Understanding customers and segmenting in an appropriate way play a vital role in business operations and effective marketing strategies. It helps target specific customer groups for increased engagement and profit. However, traditional approaches often struggle to predict future purchase patterns, especially when user data is sparse and fragmented across multiple sources. This research proposes a novel clustering-based multitask classification method to address these limitations. We integrated the Recency, Frequency Monetary (RFM) model to cluster customers based on their purchase patterns from various purchase categories (tickets, merchandise, fan club membership) to create a more comprehensive understanding of loyalty for a professional basketball team in Japan. The proposed model predicts a customer&amp;rsquo;s segment across all purchase categories, implying the potential relationships between each category. Initial results demonstrate that the model effectively analyzes purchase behaviors, offering actionable insights to enhance marketing strategies.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Search Results</title>
      <link>https://seoyeongpark.github.io/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://seoyeongpark.github.io/search/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This file exists solely to respond to /search URL with the related &lt;code&gt;search&lt;/code&gt; layout template.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;No content shown here is rendered, all content is based in the template layouts/page/search.html&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Setting a very low sitemap priority will tell search engines this is not important content.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This implementation uses Fusejs, jquery and mark.js&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;initial-setup&#34;&gt;Initial setup&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Search  depends on additional output content type of JSON in config.toml&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-fallback&#34; data-lang=&#34;fallback&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;[outputs]&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;  home = [&amp;#34;HTML&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;JSON&amp;#34;]&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;searching-additional-fileds&#34;&gt;Searching additional fileds&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To search additional fields defined in front matter, you must add it in 2 places.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
