<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Seoyeong Park</title>
    <link>https://seoyeongpark.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Seoyeong Park</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>utf-8</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://seoyeongpark.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Identifying Barriers Faced by Older Adults in Mobile App Usage (under review)</title>
      <link>https://seoyeongpark.github.io/publications/elderly-accessibility/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seoyeongpark.github.io/publications/elderly-accessibility/</guid>
      <description>Abstract As life expectancy increases and the elderly population grows, the older adults&amp;rsquo; embrace of technology is highlighted in modern society as one of the key factors in closing the digital gap to prevent discrimination among different age groups. In this paper, we explore the psychological and technological factors that influence mobile usage by older users. In addition, we describe our observation about the supplement points of the present accessibility guidelines for older adults to embed them into the mobile environment to improve their independence and quality of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Detecting correlation between emotional changes and writing style based on historical social media postings using NLP</title>
      <link>https://seoyeongpark.github.io/research/emotion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 19:33:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seoyeongpark.github.io/research/emotion/</guid>
      <description>Abstract  Discovering discernible changes in writing style depending on emotional shifts in online communication and social media posts Envisioning a conditional random field (CRF) that captures transitions in emotional states to create an empathetic language suggestion model that generates comforting and supportive responses to users  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reinforcement learning model for multi-objective food allocation optimization system</title>
      <link>https://seoyeongpark.github.io/research/scc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 1969 19:33:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seoyeongpark.github.io/research/scc/</guid>
      <description>Abstract  Developing an RL-based user modeling framework for food agences to optimizae food allocation to end-users by capturing, shaping user needs and preferences, and nudging shifting tastes via persuasive messaging. Approaching as a multi-stakeholder recommendation system to consider benefits of both users and providers.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Course scheduling with CSP</title>
      <link>https://seoyeongpark.github.io/projects/courseschedulingcsp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seoyeongpark.github.io/projects/courseschedulingcsp/</guid>
      <description>Project design The objective of this project is to help students design and simulate their course schedules based on given the dataset of the course listing.
The course scheduler is considered as a constraint satisfaction problem by checking schedule conflicts and requirements to generate a feasible schedule with minimizing unsatisfied preference. We have assumed that every student must enroll as a full-time student, and they have a maximum credit limit. Each course contains information about time, prerequisites, instructor, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discord bot - StockImpulse</title>
      <link>https://seoyeongpark.github.io/projects/stockimpulse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seoyeongpark.github.io/projects/stockimpulse/</guid>
      <description>Project design StockImpulse is a fast and easy to use discord bot for getting stock information. This means that users will have access to information about US stocks from their discord account. StockImpulse also allows users to look up information about crypto currencies. StockImpulse allows for up to 60 stock requests every minute and 50 requests every 10 minutes for cryptocurrency.
Instruction Refer to the official instruction
APIs  The Finnhub API is used for information regarding stocks alongside the finnhub-python python package.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slash - Price comparison web</title>
      <link>https://seoyeongpark.github.io/projects/slash/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seoyeongpark.github.io/projects/slash/</guid>
      <description>Project design Slash is a website that scrapes the most popular e-commerce websites to get the best deals on the searched items across these websites.
 Fast: With slash, you can save over 50% of your time by comparing deals across websites within seconds Easy: Slash uses very easy commands to filter, sort and search your items Powerful: Quickly alter the commands to get desired results Informative: Provides the information about items through an email with attached csv file  Instruction Refer to the official instruction</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search Results</title>
      <link>https://seoyeongpark.github.io/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seoyeongpark.github.io/search/</guid>
      <description>This file exists solely to respond to /search URL with the related search layout template.
No content shown here is rendered, all content is based in the template layouts/page/search.html
Setting a very low sitemap priority will tell search engines this is not important content.
This implementation uses Fusejs, jquery and mark.js
Initial setup Search depends on additional output content type of JSON in config.toml
[outputs]home = [&amp;#34;HTML&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;JSON&amp;#34;]Searching additional fileds To search additional fields defined in front matter, you must add it in 2 places.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>