<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Behavior on Seoyeong Park</title>
    <link>https://seoyeongpark.github.io/tags/behavior/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Behavior on Seoyeong Park</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>utf-8</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://seoyeongpark.github.io/tags/behavior/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Clustering-based Multitask Classification for Predictive Consumer Behavior Modeling</title>
      <link>https://seoyeongpark.github.io/research/nagoya/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 09:33:43 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seoyeongpark.github.io/research/nagoya/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Understanding customers and segmenting in an appropriate way play a vital role in business operations and effective marketing strategies. It helps target specific customer groups for increased engagement and profit. However, traditional approaches often struggle to predict future purchase patterns, especially when user data is sparse and fragmented across multiple sources. This research proposes a novel clustering-based multitask classification method to address these limitations. We integrated the RFM model to cluster customers based on their purchase patterns from various purchase categories (tickets, merchandise, fan club membership) to create a more comprehensive understanding of loyalty for a professional basketball team in Japan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Influencing behavior change: adaptive interventions using cognitive mechanism</title>
      <link>https://seoyeongpark.github.io/research/adaptive/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seoyeongpark.github.io/research/adaptive/</guid>
      <description>Summary and goal  TBC  Abstract  Publications  Paper  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Identifying Barriers Faced by Older Adults in Mobile App Usage</title>
      <link>https://seoyeongpark.github.io/research/elderly-accessibility/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://seoyeongpark.github.io/research/elderly-accessibility/</guid>
      <description>Abstract As life expectancy increases and the elderly population grows, the older adults&amp;rsquo; embrace of technology is highlighted in modern society as one of the key factors in closing the digital gap to prevent discrimination among different age groups. In this paper, we explore the psychological and technological factors that influence mobile usage by older users. In addition, we describe our observation about the supplement points of the present accessibility guidelines for older adults to embed them into the mobile environment to improve their independence and quality of life.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>